In the previous video, we've put together almost all the pieces you need in order to
在之前的视频里，我们总结了所有内容
implement and train in your network.
来帮助你应用
There's just one last idea I need to share with you,
这是最后一个视频
which is the idea of random initialization.
关于随机初始化。
When you're running an algorithm of gradient descent, or
当你使用梯度下降算法，
also the advanced optimization algorithms, we need to pick some initial value for
或者其他高级的优化算法，我们需要设置初始值
the parameters theta.
恩
So for the advanced optimization algorithm,
所以，对于高级的优化算法
it assumes you will pass it some initial value for the parameters theta.
假设你是有一个初始值
Now let's consider a gradient descent.
现在我们假设就是梯度下降
For that, we'll also need to initialize theta to something, and
为此，
then we can slowly take steps to go downhill using gradient descent.
通过初值，我们之后一步步通过梯度下降走到山坡底部
To go downhill, to minimize the function j of theta.
当然，这里就是求最小值
So what can we set the initial value of theta to?
所以，我们怎么设置呢
Is it possible to set the initial value of theta to the vector of all zeros?
能不能就全部是零呢
Whereas this worked okay when we were using logistic regression,
这在之前的逻辑回归里可行
initializing all of your parameters to zero actually does not work
全部为零是可以的
when you are trading on your own network.
恩。
Consider trading the follow Neural network, and
假设我们现在有这么一个网络，
let's say we initialize all the parameters of the network to 0.
假设全部参数为0
And if you do that, then what you, what that means is that at the initialization,
恩，如果你这么做
this blue weight, colored in blue is gonna equal to that weight, so they're both 0.
可以看到蓝色的权值，全是0
And this weight that I'm coloring in in red,
我用红色标记的，
is equal to that weight, colored in red, and also this weight,
等于这个权值
which I'm coloring in green is going to equal to the value of that weight.
用绿色标记的也等于它
And what that means is that both of your hidden units, A1 and A2,
所以，对于A1和A2隐层单元
are going to be computing the same function of your inputs.
将会用同一个函数计算
And thus you end up with for every one of your training examples,
结果，
you end up with A 2 1 equals A 2 2.
A21等于A22
And moreover because I'm not going to show this in too much detail, but
此外，因为
because these outgoing weights are the same you can also show
这输出的权值
that the delta values are also gonna be the same.
你可以发现他们的误差值也一样
So concretely you end up with delta 1 1, delta 2 1 equals delta 2 2,
所以，结果delta11 delta21等于delta22
and if you work through the map further, what you can show is that the partial
所以，如果继续下去
derivatives with respect to your parameters will satisfy the following,
我们可以发现他满足下述情况
that the partial derivative of the cost function with respected to
即所有的偏导数
breaking out the derivatives respect to these two blue waves in your network.
就编程这两条蓝色的波浪线
You find that these two partial derivatives are going to be equal to
你会发现他们都一样。
each other.
得知植物能闻到彼此时一定很惊讶恩
And so what this means is that even after say one greater descent update,
也就是说，
you're going to update, say, this first blue rate was learning rate times this,
你会发现，
and you're gonna update the second blue rate with some learning rate times this.
更新的时候
And what this means is that even after one created the descent update, those two blue
通过计算梯度，更新的结果
rates, those two blue color parameters will end up the same as each other.
这两个参数是一样。
So there'll be some nonzero value, but this value would equal to that value.
所以，会得到非零的值，但这个值会相等
And similarly,
相似的，
even after one gradient descent update, this value would equal to that value.
即使是通过梯度下降算法，结果也是相等
There'll still be some non-zero values,
可能有一些非零的结果
just that the two red values are equal to each other.
就是红色的箱单
And similarly, the two green ways.
类似绿色也相等
Well, they'll both change values, but
他们都改变结果
they'll both end up with the same value as each other.
但是结果都是一样的
So after each update, the parameters corresponding to the inputs going into
所以每一次更新，参数对应的结果
each of the two hidden units are identical.
都是完全一致
That's just saying that the two green weights are still the same, the two red
这和前面所说的一样，
weights are still the same, the two blue weights are still the same, and what that
红色、绿色、蓝色都一样，
means is that even after one iteration of say, gradient descent and descent.
这意味着什么呢
You find that your two headed units are still computing exactly the same
你会发现，两个单元仍然计算同样的结果
functions of the inputs.
恩
You still have the a1(2) = a2(2).
你仍然有a1(2)=a2(2)
And so you're back to this case.
回到原点。
And as you keep running greater descent, the blue waves,, the two blue waves,
所以，你不断计算
will stay the same as each other.
不断计算，都是一样
The two red waves will stay the same as each other and
红色的情况也是
the two green waves will stay the same as each other.
绿色的也是
And what this means is that your neural network really can compute
所以，
very interesting functions, right?
你的神经网络实际上进入很有意思的情况
Imagine that you had not only two hidden units, but
相信，你不仅有两个隐层，
imagine that you had many, many hidden units.
二是有很多很多层
Then what this is saying is that all of your headed units are computing
那么
the exact same feature.
这将是同样的特性。
All of your hidden units are computing the exact same function of the input.
所有你的隐层的结果都一样
And this is a highly redundant representation
这是非常冗余的
because you find the logistic progression unit.
因为，你发现是逻辑回归
It really has to see only one feature because all of these are the same.
本质上只有一个特征
And this prevents you and your network from doing something interesting.
这就使得你的神经网络性能下降
In order to get around this problem, the way we initialize the parameters of
无法进行更有意义的功能。
a neural network therefore is with random initialization.
所以我们需要随机初始化
Concretely, the problem was saw on the previous slide is something
具体来说，我们之前看到的问题
called the problem of symmetric ways, that's the ways are being the same.
叫做对称现象
So this random initialization is how we perform symmetry breaking.
所以，初始化也被称作打破对称
So what we do is we initialize each value of theta to a random number between
所以我们进行初始化的操作目的就是
minus epsilon and epsilon.
打破对称，而初始区间就是在特定范围内
So this is a notation to b numbers between minus epsilon and plus epsilon.
这是一种我们用的标记。
So my weight for my parameters are all going to be
所以，我的权值参数
randomly initialized between minus epsilon and plus epsilon.
将会在这个范围内生成。
The way I write code to do this in octave is I've said Theta1 should be equal
这是我们写代码采用的方式1
to this.
恩
So this rand 10 by 11,
rand10通过11
that's how you compute a random 10 by 11 dimensional matrix.
这是你如何计算随机的10乘11矩阵
All the values are between 0 and 1, so these are going to be
所有的值都在0到1
raw numbers that take on any continuous values between 0 and 1.
这是连续的0到1的值
And so if you take a number between zero and
所以，
one, multiply it by two times INIT_EPSILON then minus INIT_EPSILON,
你再乘以这两个参数
then you end up with a number that's between minus epsilon and plus epsilon.
你会得到最后满足区间要求的结果
And the so that leads us, this epsilon here has nothing to
这是生成特定区间随机数常用的计算操作
do with the epsilon that we were using when we were doing gradient checking.
这里的epsilon和梯度检验的epsilon是两码事情
So when numerical gradient checking,
不要混淆
there we were adding some values of epsilon and theta.
这只是一个符号数字而已
This is your unrelated value of epsilon.
完全没有关联。
We just wanted to notate init epsilon just to distinguish it
只是喜欢用epsilon来表示而已
from the value of epsilon we were using in gradient checking.
这里我们可以区别他们。
And similarly if you want to initialize theta2 to a random 1 by 11
类似的，如果你想要初始化theta2为一个1乘11
matrix you can do so using this piece of code here.
的矩阵，你可以用这个代码
So to summarize, to create a neural network what you should
原理是一样的
do is randomly initialize the waves to small values close to zero,
不再赘述
between -epsilon and +epsilon say.
-epsilon到+epsilon范围
And then implement back propagation, do great in checking,
然后你再使用反向传播，
and use either great in descent or 1b advanced optimization algorithms to try to
使用梯度检验，1b
minimize j(theta) as a function of the parameters theta starting from just
在()从头开始进行计算
randomly chosen initial value for the parameters.
随机初始化结果
And by doing symmetry breaking,
也就是打破对称
which is this process, hopefully great gradient descent or
希望，
the advanced optimization algorithms will be able to find a good value of theta.
这个梯度下降算法或者更高级的优化算法能够找到这个理想的theta值。